A Guide to the Papers of Homer Stille Cummings, ca.1850-1955
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
- SERIES III: CORRESPONDENCE OF THE ATTORNEY GENERAL AND POST-ATTORNEY GENERAL, 1933-1956
  - Correspondence of Homer Stille Cummings - General "Ra-Re" 1934 September-1956 August (Box 144)
  - Correspondence of Homer Stille Cummings - "Rh-Ry" 1934 September-1956 August, 2 folders (Box 145)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Racketeering, Kidnapping 1933 July-November (Box 145)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Senator George L. Radcliffe 1936 March-1937 June (Box 145)
  - Correspondence of Homer Stille Cummings re: James Ragland 1955 August-1956 August (Box 145)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Railroads 1934 January-1938 May (Box 145)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Julian D. Rainey 1938 September-October (Box 145)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Robert L. Ramsay 1936 January-1937 April (Box 145)
  - Attorney General Personal File - William H. Ramsey 1937 January-1938 August (Box 145)
  - Correspondence of Homer Stille Cummings re: Edmund Randolph 1941 April-May (Box 145)
  - Attorney General Personal File - William L. Random 1936 August-1949 April (Box 145)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Lady Reading 1936 January-1945 May (Box 145)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Real America(magazine) 1934 June-November (Box 145)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Realization Coal Company 1933 July (Box 146)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Receipts for insured packages 1934 February-1937 August (Box 146)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Recess appointments 1934 July-1938 May (Box 146)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Reciprocal Trade Agreement with Switzerland 1935 February-1937 October (Box 146)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Red Cross 1934 April (Box 146)
  - Attorney General Personal File - David A. Reed 1932 July (Box 146)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Eugene E. Reed 1933 March-1940 December (Box 146)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Stanley Reed 1934 December-1944 June (Box 146)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Christian F. Reisner 1933 November-1940 December (Box 146)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Mihran Renjihan 1937 August-September (Box 146)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Reorganization Committee 1936 August-1937 January (Box 146)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Reorganization of Justice Department 1933 December-1938 October (Box 146)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Resettlement Administration, Delays in 1936 March-September (Box 146)
  - Correspondence of Homer Stille Cummings re: Resignation Banquet 1938 November-1939 January (Box 146)
  - Correspondence of Homer Stille Cummings re: Resignation Banquet 1939 January-April (Box 147)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Resignation from the Cabinet 1938 November (Box 147)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Resolutions, Miscellaneous Adopted at Conventions 1936 April-October (Box 147)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Retirement, compulsory at age seventy 1938 November (Box 147)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Retirement, Supreme Court Justices 1936 January-1938 January (Box 147)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Revenue Act 1936 September (Box 147)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Robert A. Reynolds 1935 March-1938 March (Box 147)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Senator Robert R. Reynolds 1934 December-1943 October (Box 147)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Thomas S. Rhea 1937 December-1941 August (Box 147)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Donald Richberg 1935 May-1956 April (Box 147)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Stephens Rippey 1938 May-1941 June (Box 147)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Henry R. Rittenberg 1935 December-1937 January (Box 147)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Mr. & Mrs. Addison Robb 1938 April (Box 147)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Hampton Robb 1934 June-1935 January (Box 147)
  - Attorney General Personal File - N.G. Robertson 1933 May-1938 May (Box 147)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Hugh B. Robinson 1935 October-1937 September (Box 147)
  - Attorney General Personal File - James J. Robinson 1943 June-1955 January (Box 147)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Joseph T. Robinson 1934 January-1955 June (Box 148)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Robinson-Patman Act 1936 July (Box 148)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Rocky Mountain Power Company 1936 April (Box 148)
  - Attorney General Personal File - John rodemeyer 1933 September-1935 November (Box 148)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Rollins College 1936 December-1955 July (Box 148)
  - Correspondence of Homer Stille Cummings - Elliott Roosevelt 1949 July-August (Box 148)
  - Attorney General Personal File - James Roosevelt 1936 May-1937 June (Box 148)
  - Correspondence of Homer Stille Cummings - John Roosevelt 1938 May-June (Box 148)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Daniel C. Roper (landlord) 1933 March-1955 August (Box 148)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Edward C. Rose 1941 October-1952 May (Box 148)
  - Attorney General Personal File - James N. Rosenberg 1939 May-June (Box 149)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Samuel I. Rosenman 1933 July-1946 March (Box 149)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Ira C. Rothgerber 1934 April-1956 August (Box 149)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Dr. L.S. Rowe 1934 April-1942 May (Box 149)
  - Attorney General Personal File - George P. Rowell 1933 June-1837 July (Box 149)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Robert J. Ryle 1933 March-1945 May (Box 149)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Thomas J. Ryle 1933 June-1954 February (Box 149)
  - Attorney General Personal File - General "Sac-Sco" 1933 April-1956 August, 2 folders (Box 149)
  - Attorney General Personal File - General "Sco-Sh" 1933 April-1956 August, 2 folders (Box 149)
  - Correspondence of Homer Stille Cummings - General "Sh-Stew" 1933 April-1956 August, 6 folders (Box 150)
  - Correspondence of Homer Stille Cummings - General "Stew-Sw" 1933 April-1956 August (Box 151)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Wheeler Sammons 1934 November-1956 April (Box 151)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Eugene B. Sanger 1933 May-1941 January (Box 151)
  - Attorney General Personal File - David Sarnoff 1936 February-1939 January (Box 151)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Schechter Case 1939 April-May (Box 151)
  - Correspondence of Homer Stille Cummings - William V. Schmidt Company, Inc. 1943 February-June (Box 151)
  - Correspondence of Homer Stille Cummings re: Raymond C. Schindler 1936 January-1952 March (Box 151)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Frank D. Schroth 1939 March-1956 April (Box 151)
  - Attorney General Personal File - H.O. Schundler 1937 November-1942 August (Box 152)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Secretary of Labor Lewis B. Schwellenbach 1935 August-1945 May (Box 152)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Scotland Yard 1934 March-April (Box 152)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Scribes 1953 January-1956 July (Box 152)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Secretary of War 1936 September (Box 152)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Section 3224 (Tax Matters) 1936 January (Box 152)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Arthur Seligman 1932 November-1933 October (Box 152)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Senate Bill 4673 1936 May-June (Box 152)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Senator's Right to Practice Law 1931 August (Box 152)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Robert L. Sengle 1933 March (Box 152)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Senior Center Judges 1937 October (Box 152)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Mildred Seydell 1938 October-November (Box 152)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Morrison Shafroth 1933 June-1949 August (Box 152)
  - Correspondence of Homer Stille Cummings re: James A. Shanley 1935 February-1946 March (Box 152)
  - Attorney General Personal File - J.R. Shanley Estate 1938 October-1946 June (Box 152)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Senator Morris Sheppard 1935 August-1936 August (Box 152)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Leighton Shields n.d. (Box 152)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Arthur L. Shipman 1932 March-1937 November (Box 152)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Senator Henrik Shipstead 1935 August-1938 July (Box 152)
  - Attorney General Personal File - The "Shilver Shirts" (Asheville, NC anti-semitic group) 1938 May (Box 152)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Congressman William I Sirovish 1935 May-1945 March (Box 152)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Sit Down Strikes 1937 March (Box 153)
  - Correspondence of Homer Stille Cummings - John Skaggs, jr. 1951 April-June 19 (Box 153)
  - Correspondence of Homer Stille Cummings - John Skaggs, Jr. 1951 June 21-July (Box 153)
  - Correspondence of Homer Stille Cummings - John Skaggs, Jr. 1951 August-1952 August, 2 folders (Box 153)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Robert C. Skinner 1936 August-September (Box 153)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Ambassador Robert P. Skinner 1933 March-1954 December (Box 153)
  - Correspondence of Homer Stille Cummings - Skytop Lodge 1942 August-1956 January (Box 153)
  - Correspondence of Homer Stille Cummings - Lou N. Small 1944 June-1946 March (Box 153)
  - Correspondence of Homer Stille Cummings - Small Business [ca. 1950] (Box 153)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Senator William H. Smathers 1938 October (Box 153)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Rev. G.K. Smith 1936 July-August (Box 153)
  - Attorney General Personal File - J. Francis Smith 1934 March-1940 April (Box 153)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Paul Smith 1938 October (Box 153)
  - Attorney General Personal File - T.V. Smith 1940 January-September (Box 153)
  - Correspondence of Homer Stille Cummings - Wilbert Snow 1944 July-1956 August, 2 folders (Box 154)
  - Correspondence of Homer Stille Cummings - Ralph M. Snyder 1942 May-1951 August (Box 154)
  - Correspondence of Homer Stille Cummings - Social Security 1954 February (Box 154)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Social Security Act 1936 November-1938 December (Box 154)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Societe Suisse (Swiss Case) 1937 January-1939 June (Box 154)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Solicitor General, Applicants for 1938 January (Box 154)
  - Correspondence of Homer Stille Cummings - Sonotone Corp. 1952 March-1954 December (Box 154)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Nicholas Soussanin 1936 May (Box 154)
  - Attorney General Personal File - South Side Estates 1935 April-1939 October (Box 154)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Space in Justice Department Building 1936 April-1937 May (Box 154)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Spanish Embargo 1938 March-December (Box 155)
  - Correspondence of Homer Stille Cummings - Spanish Embassy 1949 January-February; 1951 January (Box 155)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Spanish Silver Case 1938 September-October (Box 155)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Speeches, Printing of 1935 February-1936 January (Box 155)
  - Attorney General Personal File - G.G. Speer & W.C. Speer 1933 July-August (Box 155)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Max Spelke 1938 December-1944 July, 2 folders (Box 155)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Walter P. Stacy 1937 August (Box 155)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Leonardo Stagnaro 1932 September-1956 January, 2 folders (Box 155)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Ingram M. Stainback 1936 September-1951 October (Box 155)
  - Correspondence of Homer Stille Cummings - Stamford Bar Association Banquet 1944 June-December (Box 155)
  - Correspondence of Homer Stille Cummings - John S. Stanley 1946 July-1951 July (Box 155)
  - Attorney General Personal File - State Compacts 1936 November-1937 January (Box 155)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Daniel F. Steck 1937 March-May (Box 155)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Steel Industry 1937 April (Box 155)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Frederick Steiwer 1938 February (Box 155)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Albert Lee Stephens 1936 September-1939 September (Box 155)
  - Correspondence of Homer Stille Cummings - Harold M. Stephens 1933 August-1955 June, 2 folders (Box 156)
  - Attorney General Personal File - J. David Stern 1934 January-1942 August (Box 156)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Adlai Stevenson 1954 August-1956 August (Box 156)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Charles E. Stewart 1934 April-1953 November (Box 156)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Harry W. Stewart, Jr. 1949 November-1956 August (Box 156)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Henry L. Stimson 1940 July (Box 156)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Marshall Stimson 1933 March-1935 March (Box 156)
  - Correspondence of Homer Stille Cummings - Alexandro Stoianovici 1950 May-1951 June (Box 156)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Justice Harlan F. Stone 1936 January-1946 June (Box 157)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Judge Kimbrough Stone 1935 August-1951 January (Box 157)
  - Attorney General Personal File - R.B. Strassburger 1937 August-October (Box 157)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Ambassador Jesse Isidor Straus 1933 March-1936 October (Box 157)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Strike Breaking Statute 1936 September (Box 157)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Suburban Trust Company 1947 May-1955 June (Box 157)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Subversive Groups, List of 1947 October (Box 157)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Francis E. Sullivan, Rhode Island Political situation 1936 January (Box 157)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Jerry B. Sullivan 1933 March-1937 January (Box 157)
  - Attorney General Personal File - William Sulzer 1936 November-1937 September (Box 157)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Hatton W. Summers 1934 December-1939 June (Box 157)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Surete Nationale 1935 May (Box 157)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Survey of Release Procedures 1937 April-1939 July (Box 157)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Joseph R. Swan 1937 May (Box 157)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Claude A. Swanson 1933 December-1939 July (Box 157)
  - Attorney General Personal File - George C. Sweeney 1935 July-1940 April (Box 157)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Herbert B. Swope 1937 December-1939 March (Box 157)
  - Correspondence of Homer Stille Cummings - General "Ta-Ty" 1932 September-1955 November, 3 folders (Box 158)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Tax Bill of 1936 1936 February (Box 158)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Tax Evasion 1937 June (Box 158)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Tax Exemption 1937 June-1938 September (Box 158)
  - Memoranda of Homer Stille Cummings re: Taxes, Wills, etc. 1948 October (Box 158)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Teamsters' Local 708 (re: violatons of Anti-Trust and Anti-Racketeering Acts), also Teamsters' Strike of 1933 1933 November-1937 November (Box 159)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Richmond Temple 1935 October-1938 May (Box 159)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Richard A. Templeton 1934 November-1953 January (Box 159)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Tennessee Electric Power 1938 January 24 (Box 159)
  - Attorney General Personal File - "The Tenth Old Man" 1937 February-March (Box 159)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Terminal Transportation System 1934 June (Box 159)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Texas Company Oil Tank Ships 1937 August (Box 159)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Thomas D. Thacher 1933 May-1934 October (Box 159)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Thefts of coal in Pennsylvania 1936 April-May (Box 159)
  - Attorney General Personal File - "They All Come Out" (prison movie) 1938 February-1939 July (Box 159)
  - Correspondence & Memoranda of Homer Stille Cummings - E.S. Thomas 1939 March-1942 August (Box 159)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Edwin S. Thomas 1933 March-1938 October (Box 159)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Senator Elmer Thomas 1936 December-1944 December (Box 159)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Seth Thomas 1935 August-1936 December (Box 159)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Norman Thomas 1938 July-October (Box 159)
  - Correspondence of Homer Stille Cummings - Judge R.C.P. Thomas, includes papers relating to Thomas' will 1933 July-1943 April (Box 159)
  - Correspondence of Homer Stille Cummings - Invitations and acceptance re: a party in honor of Ambasassador and Senora de Thomen, includes a guest list 1948 May-June (Box 159)
  - Correspondence of Homer Stille Cummings - Invitations and acceptances re: a party in honor of Ambasassador and Senora de THomen, includes a guest list 1948 May-June, 2 folders (Box 160)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Clarence E. Thompson (Box 160)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Huston Thompson 1933 March-1938 July (Box 160)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Mrs. Alice Mead Thorp 1935 May-June (Box 160)
  - Correspondence of Homer Stille Cummings - William H. Timbers (Box 160)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Daniel J. Tobin (President, Teamster's Union) 1933 October-1939 December (Box 161)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Maximilian Toch 1937 February-March (Box 161)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Joseph C. Todd 1936 April-May (Box 161)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Edgar B. Tolman 1936 June-1939 December (Box 161)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Joseph M. Tone 1933 June-1945 July (Box 161)
  - Correspondence of Homer Stille Cummings re: Proposed membership of Harry A. Toulmin, Jr. in the American Law Institute 1954 October-1955 May (Box 161)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Robina P. Townes 1933 April-1941 June (Box 161)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Trade Agreement Act 1971 May (Box 161)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Smith Trimble 1936 September (Box 161)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Walter Trohan 1937 June-1938 February (Box 161)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Fred Trotta 1932 June-1937 April (Box 161)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Philip Troup 1933 July-1936 September (Box 162)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Harry S. Truman 1940 August-1956 March (Box 162)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Rexford G. Tugwell 1936 December-1937 January (Box 162)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Loretto Tully 1934 September-1941 April (Box 162)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Joseph P. Tumulty 1934 December-1946 June (Box 162)
  - Memoranda of Homer Stille Cummings - Tunick Brothers 1948 August (Box 162)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Gene Tunney 1933 June-1954 November (Box 162)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Leon G. Turrov 1938 June (Box 162)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Tydings-Miller Bill 1937 January-July (Box 162)
  - Correspondence of Homer Stille Cummings - General "U" 1936 April-1956 March (Box 162)
  - Attorney General Personal File - U.S. Court of Appeals for the District of Columbia re: Appointments 1937 March 18-August 15 (Box 162)
  - Attorney General Personal File - U.S. Court of Appeals for the District of Columbia re: Appointments 1937 March-1938 January (Box 163)
  - Attorney General Personal File - U.S. Court of Customs and Patent Appeals 1937 November (Box 163)
  - Attorney General Personal File - United States Law Review 1937 March-1939 May (Box 163)
  - Attorney General Personal File - University Club, Washington, D.C. 1933 March-1938 May (Box 163)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Samuel Untermeyer 1919 January-1934 March (Box 163)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Donald Updike 1940 May-1952 October (Box 163)
  - Correspondence of Homer Stille Cummings - Utah Construction Company 1952 December-1953 January (Box 163)
  - Correspondence of Homer Stille Cummings - General "V" 1934 November-1956 June (Box 163)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Senator Arthur H. Vandenberg 1935 August-1950 June (Box 163)
  - Correspondence of Homer Stille Cummings - Chief Justice Arthur T. Vanderbilt 1937 December-1952 August (Box 163)
  - Correspondence of Homer Stille Cummings - Chief Justice Arthur T. Vanderbilt 1952 August-1956 June, 2 folders (Box 164)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Justice Willis Van Devanter 1937 March-May (Box 164)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Peter & Gus Vanech 1933 September-1955 March (Box 164)
  - Correspondence of Homer Stille Cummings - Mr. & mrs. Otto Vega 1952 December-1953 January (Box 164)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Thomas Veitch 1936 oct-1937 January (Box 164)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Veto Power of the President 1937 March (Box 164)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Reed Vetterli 1936 July-1938 July (Box 164)
  - Correspondence of Homer Stille Cummings - Chief Justice Fred M. Vinson 1944 April-1954 October (Box 164)
  - Correspondence of Homer Stille Cummings - Pasqual Vioni 1939 July-1955 April (Box 164)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Virgin Islands 1934 October-1936 August (Box 164)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Lt. Frank Verilli 1933 March-1947 January (Box 164)
  - Correspondence of Homer Stille Cummings - General "Wad-Wof" 1933 December-1956 September, 4 folders (Box 165)
  - Correspondence of Homer Stille Cummings - General "Wol-Wy" 1933 December-1956 September (Box 166)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Senator Robert F. Wagner 1934 September-1945 October (Box 166)
  - Attorney General Personal File - George Waldo 1934 January-1957 February (Box 166)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Frank C. Walker 1933 March-1944 August (Box 166)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Henry A. Wallace 1934 January-1949 (Box 166)
  - Correspondence of Homer Stille Cummings re: Henry A. Wallace - Memoranda re: Mathematical doodle 1939 December (Box 166)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Wallace & Cummings - Financial Matters and Business Conditions (Box 166)
  - Attorney General Personal File - John Walsh 1937 May-June (Box 166)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Thomas J. Walsh Portrait 1933 February-1936 April (Box 166)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Franklyn Waltman 1937 May-1943 June (Box 166)
  - Correspondence of Homer Stille Cummings - Arthur Walworth 1951 February-1956 September (Box 166)
  - Correspondence of Homer Stille Cummings - War Finance Committee 1943 April-August (Box 166)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Justice Wardell 1936 May-1944 June (Box 166)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Warner Hall 1936 January (Box 166)
  - Correspondence of Homer Stille Cummings - Washington Heart Association 1949 January (Box 166)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Washington News Company 1952 December-1954 November (Box 166)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Archibald R. Watson 1937 December-1938 April (Box 166)
  - Correspondence of Homer Stille Cummings - Edwin M. Watson 1939 December-1941 January (Box 166)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Felthan Watson 1935 January-1946 October (Box 166)
  - Attorney General Personal File - James E. Watson 1935 February-November (Box 166)
  - Attorney General Personal File - John Wattawa 1934 November-1955 August (Box 166)
  - Correspondence of Homer Stille Cummings - Jacob Webb 1944 July-1949 April (Box 167)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Weirton Steel Company 1934 January-August (Box 167)
  - Attorney General Personal File - J.E. Welch 1936 May-June (Box 167)
  - Correspondence of Homer Stille Cummings - West Coast Line 1953 July-1955 July (Box 167)
  - Attorney General Personal File - James J. Whalen 1938 June-1940 December (Box 167)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Senator Burton K. Wheeler 1935 August-1940 (Box 167)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Senator Wheeler (appointments) 1937 June (Box 167)
  - Attorney General Personal File - Charles Whelan 1935 August-1936 December (Box 167)